Mr Bharat Shah

31/11/1988 ● Employment visa ● Al Falah Stree, Abu Dhabi 2419, United Arab Emirates ● 0527116634 ● akashche72@gmail.com ● https://www.linkedin.com/in/b-k-shah-9403438a/

Profile

Object orientated six years of total experiences in Project Management. Excellent customer service, information gathering, budgeting, planning, executing plan. Provides timely, accurate and relevant project and program reporting. Ensure projects are delivered within the defined scope, quality, time and cost requirements. Accountable for delivering programs and projects which include large/complex/cross-functional strategic and/or technical initiatives that may extend across businesses. Worked with verity of Enterprise's, Excellent Capabilities, Brand Development, Identify Target Customers, Set Clear Objectives, Visual Design and Web Development Strategy, Solid Content Strategy, Promotion Strategy, Engagement Strategy, Conversion Strategy, Measure & Analyze to Establish ROI. Digital Marketing, SEO, SEM, PPC, Google Analytics, Agile, Salesforce, Jira, Experience with the entire project life-cycle (requirements, information architecture, prototyping, management of design, development & QA). Coding Skill as well.

Work experience

03/2011 - 02/2013

Digital Customer Service Executive

Uniweb Technologies Pty Ltd., Nepal, Kathmandu

Project Management: Coordination of all aspects of a project, which includes project planning, execution, timing, quality, cost and early identification of potential issues.

Identifying stakeholders and clients, evaluate their interests.

Embed project risk awareness, proactively identifying and raising control deficiencies and driving diligent and sustainable risk remediation.

Act as Scrum Master or Product Owner when required.

People Management: Ensuring assignment of work to the teams and efficient use of resources within the teams.

Quality Management: Ensuring that Dash project quality standards are met for each project deliverable

Communication: Establish and maintain effective communication channels with project stakeholders.

Reporting: Providing the Dash Core Group stakeholders with transparent, accurate and regular information regarding the status of project deliveries.

Reporting: Providing Project Portfolio Manager with regular information regarding the status of project deliveries.

Delivery Management: Participating in Dash delivery processes processes definition and maintenance.

Delivery Management: Ensuring that the project follows Dash Project Management Framework (PMF) and industry principles and standards.

Collaboration: Working collaboratively in a distributed team environment to reach ideal outcomes and solutions.

Collaboration: Participating internal PM team meetings on regular basis.

03/2013 - 01/2015

Digital Account Manager (Web and Software Development)

Design Programm Host Pvt. Ltd., Nepal, Kathmandu

Accountable for delivering programs and projects which include large/complex/cross-functional strategic and/or technical initiatives that may extend across businesses. Provides core project management expertise for the full lifecycle of initiatives, including but not limited to: project planning, initiation, resourcing, execution, monitoring, control and completion.

Provides timely, accurate and relevant project and program reporting. Ensure projects are delivered within the defined scope, quality, time and cost requirements.

Establish strong business partnerships within and outside of the Customer Office to resolve issues quickly and advance efforts expeditiously.

Facilitates engagement with internal and external stakeholders, ensuring strategic alignment, clear understanding of project goals and focus on delivering meaningful outcomes.

May include management responsibility of other project managers including employees and

consultants as well as on-shore and off-shore resources.

02/2015 - 06/2016

Digital Account Manager

Crossover Pvt. Ltd., Nepal, Kathmandu

Coordinate project activities with various business stakeholders including; Marketing, Merchandising, Creative, Web Development, QA and third party suppliers.

Own the product catalog photography and attribution pipeline. Understand the flow calendar of new products to the site and maintain the milestones required to ensure the products can

launch as soon as they are stocked. Drive completion of the tasks.

Develop and own the marketing plan for launching new, and updating existing, content; including site updates, seasonal refreshes, emails promotional banners, landing pages and special projects.

Manage and oversee the end to end workflow as it relates to digital projects including development of marketing briefs, digital asset management and execution of online campaigns.

Optimize, publish and maintain assets.

Manage overall project organization to ensure requirements and project deliverable dates are clearly communicated to the product and account leads.

Support the E-commerce web team in prioritization and implementation of new and enhanced website functionality.

05/2017 - 10/2017

Digital Project Manager (Temporary)

Icon Advertising LLC, Dubai, UAE

Serve as a part of a client relationship team addressing the varied and changing needs of clients.

Support team lead with managing client expectations, troubleshooting and addressing issues before they become problems.

Carefully maintain program schedules to ensure activities, campaigns and events are flawlessly executed and accomplished on time and on budget.

Compile comprehensive meeting records and prepare and share meeting recaps with relevant attendees.

Work with your colleagues, to create compelling presentations and sell in plans for clients and prospective clients for a wide variety of projects.

Working closely with your colleagues to develop innovative and impactful social media campaigns and results.

Be a part of an integrated team across multiple office.

02/2018 - present

Digital Account Manager

Iptikar Publishing and Distribution , Abu Dhabi, UAE

Maintain a broad technical understanding of the Criteo platform.

Build strong client relationships with proactive, thoughtful and poised communication. Translate business objectives into technical configuration.

Solve client problems using a variety of analytical and technical tools.

Develop innovative solutions, troubleshoot client-side code, query databases and analyze results.

Drive product development by presenting client feedback to product teams.

Evangelize new products, and assist clients in the adoption of these features to ensure their long-term success.

Driving paid search strategy for top tier clients.

Creating roadmaps planning strategic initiatives & optimization efforts to hit client goals and targets.

Setting and hitting client targets for both volume and ROI.

Identifying and executing tasks that will have the most significant impact in hitting targets. Quantifying and prioritizing initiatives/opportunities accordingly.

Campaign monitoring to ensure the account is pacing well relative to budgets and targets. Implementing testing initiatives in key areas such as ad creatives, landing page messaging, landing page layout.

Education

03/2008 - 01/2014

Bachelor Degree In Business Studies/ Advertising/ Marketing, Project Management

Tribhuvan University, Kathmandu, Nepal

Project Management, Business Communication, Macro economics, Cost and management, Accounting,

Fundamentals or marketing, Foundations of human resource management.

Business Law, Fundamentals of Financial Management, Business Environment & Strategic , Organizational Behavior.

03/2009 - 11/2011

Diploma in Web Development.

National institute of Information Technology, Kathmandu, Nepal PHP. HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, JSON, XML, Soap Server, MySQL, SQLi, MSSQL, MariaDB, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Oracle OCI8, SQLite3, SQLite, Node.js

ORGANIZATIONAL SKILL

Digital Marketing Strategist, SEO

Marketing Strategist

Pulic relation managment, Corporate

communication, Excellent Communication Skill

Social Media Marketing,

Advertisement, SEM, PPC

Social Media Marketing Tools, Google

analytics

Excellent organizational and leadership skills with a problem-

solving ability

Positive and patient, Marketing, Management, Branding, and Content

Development

Outstanding communication and

interpersonal skills

Salesforce, jira, Asna, Github, SOAP,

REST, microservices

Excellent Customer Service skills

with focus on quality.

Good complaint management,

decision making, and problem solving

skills

Managing data and documentation,

Strong Reporting Skill

Good complaint management,

decision making, and problem solving

skills.

Credit Card Acquisition, Digital

Shopping Solution

Knowledge of various ROI analysis

systems, Photoshop

Language

English Norwegian(Bokmål)

Hindi

Professional

Professional

Fluent

Fluent

Fluent

Computer

Proficiency in PHP. HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, JSON, XML, Soap Server MySQL, MySQLi, MSSQL, MariaDB, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Oracle OCI8, SQLite3, SQLite, Node.js CURL, SOAP, REST API, Professional Others PHP API OOP, Agil, Jira, Asna, GitHub, REST, SOAP, PHP HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, Unite Testing, QA, Nodejs, Windows, Linux(Ubuntu/Centos), Mac OSX

Linux(Ubuntu/Centos), Mac OSX
Web Development and Design, SEO,
SEM

Microsoft office package, Wordpress, Magento 2.0, Joomla Enterprise Resource Planning(ERP) System, High traffic web development Hootsuit, Salesforce, CRM Tools, SSL,

HTTPS, Hash algorithms

Text

Balance is important than any growth or loss